Contact

ani.parseghian4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aniparseghian-393b66148 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking
Leadership
Direct Patient Care

Ani Parseghian

Travel Nurse at TotalMed, Inc. Arlington

Summary

Health care professional with experience in leadership, patient engagement and patient advocacy. Excellent organizational and communication skills proven by working independently as well as on team with multiple competing factors. Takes initiative when caring for patients and families, not only to advocate but to provide education, comfort and sensitivity in times of struggle or grieving.

Dedicated to provide exceptional nursing care while continuing to impact the future of our healthcare system, regardless of demographics or financial status.

Specialties: Leadership, patient advocacy, patient engagement, education, and public speaking.

Experience

TotalMed, Inc.
Travel Nurse
January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Lahey Hospital & Medical Center Registered Nurse December 2017 - January 2020 (2 years 2 months)

Arlington Public Schools
School Nurse
January 2017 - January 2020 (3 years 1 month)

Education

Simmons College
Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Nursing (2012 - 2016)